<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Terraform on Kelvin Lawson-W</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/terraform/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Terraform on Kelvin Lawson-W</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 21:56:26 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/terraform/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Terraform Test Framework: Say Goodbye to “Terraform Apply and Pray”</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2025/01/05/terraform-test-framework-say-goodbye-to-terraform-apply-and-pray/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 21:56:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2025/01/05/terraform-test-framework-say-goodbye-to-terraform-apply-and-pray/</guid>
      <description>The Terraform Test Framework Introduced in Terraform v1.6.x, The Terraform Test Framework was created to help validate infrastructure configurations before applying into any production environment. The testing framework introduces a native and built in way to define tests that you would like terraform to run when you want to implement either unit or integration testing.&#xA;In this post, we&amp;rsquo;ll dive into:&#xA;The importance of the Terraform Test Framework How the Terraform&amp;rsquo;s built-in test framework works A quick sample of writing and running Terraform Tests The Importance of the Terraform Test Framework Before it&amp;rsquo;s introduction, Infrastructure and DevOps engineers had to rely on tools like Terratest or manual verification for testing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Terraform Modules</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/2025/01/05/understanding-terraform-modules/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 21:56:26 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/2025/01/05/understanding-terraform-modules/</guid>
      <description>What are Terraform Modules? A Terraform module in it&amp;rsquo;s simplest form is a container for multiple resources that are used together. This is also a direct definition from the Hashicorp website. It’s a logical grouping of resources that can be reused across different parts of your infrastructure, helping to reduce duplication and increase ease of maintainance.&#xA;There are typically two types of modules:&#xA;Root Module: This is the top level configuration in your working directory where the resources for your primary infrastructure are defined.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
